

Tiago Carvalho

Junior Web Developer

Contact me:

Phone:

(33) 0782534174

E-mail:

tiago.carvalho.epbjc@gmail.com

Linkedin

www.linkedin.com/in/tiago-carvalhodev

Web Site:

https://tiago-carvalhodev.web.app

About me

Full-stack web developer passionate about work with over 1 years of experience, motivated and eager to learn. Used to work with agile or scrum methods. Proficient with ReactJS and Jamstack, but willing to explore all other opportunities and technologies. Available after August

Education

Aflokkat

Bachelor's in Developement and Conception of Applications

- September 2020 Present
- Realized in apprenticeship at Koalità

Aflokkat

Web and mobile application developer

• October 2020 - August 2021

Escola Profissional Bento de Jesus Caraça

Computer Systems Management and Programming Technician

• September 2016 a August de 2019

Experience

Junior Web Developer

Koalità September 2020 - Present

 Web development with Jamstack GatsbyJS a framework ReactJS as front and Sanity.io as Headless CMS and also some MERN stack.

Trainee

Koalità

May 2020 - July 2020

 Web development with Jamstack GatsbyJS a framework ReactJS as front and Sanity.io as Headless CMS.

Trainee

Legendary People + ideas January 2019 - March 2019

- Javascript Canvas development
- IT support

Trainee

FC Porto Serviços partilhados, S.A March 2017 - June 2017

- Help Desk
- IT support

Skills

JavaScript, HTML/CSS, PHP, Python, MySQL, GIT, mongoDB, GraphQL, JSON, MVC, ReactJS, TailwindCSS, NodeJS, Sass, AngularJS

Languages:

Português - Native Inglês - Fluent Francês - Fluent